Guide to the Yale College Records of the Dean
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Records of Horace Taft as dean, 1965-1980; Accession 1985-A-014
  - 1963-1980
    - Linguistics (Box 15, Folder 271 - 272)
    - Literary Magazine, Yale (Box 15, Folder 273)
    - Literature Major (Box 15, Folder 274 - 275)
    - Lord Committee -- Administrative Services (Box 15, Folder 276)
    - Mathematics (Box 15, Folder 278 - 279)
    - Mellon Foundation (Box 15, Folder 280)
    - Military Programs (Box 15, Folder 281)
    - Miller Memo (Box 15, Folder 282)
    - Minority Students (Box 16, Folder 283 - 286)
    - Movimento Estudantil Chicano de Aztlan (MEChA) (Box 16, Folder 287 - 288)
    - National Humanities Institute (Box 16, Folder 289)
    - National Science Foundation (Box 16, Folder 290)
    - New England Association of Schools and Colleges (Box 16, Folder 291)
    - New England Deans ' Association (Box 16, Folder 292)
    - New Haven High Schools Program (Box 16, Folder 293 - 294)
    - New York Academy of Sciences (Box 16, Folder 295)
    - News Release (Box 16, Folder 296)
    - Operations (Box 16, Folder 297 - 298)
    - Parking (Box 16, Folder 299)
    - Personnel (Box 16, Folder 300 - 301)
    - Phi Beta Kappa (Box 16, Folder 302 - 303)
    - Physical Plant (Box 16, Folder 304)
    - Political Union (Box 16, Folder 305)
    - Pre-College Preparatory Program, 1976-1977 (Box 16, Folder 306)
    - President's Office (Box 16, Folder 307 - 308)
    - Priorities and Planning (Box 16, Folder 309)
    - Provost's Office (Box 16, Folder 310)
    - Psychology (Box 16, Folder 311 - 312)
    - Publication Series, Yale College, 1976-1979 (Box 17, Folder 313)
    - Puerto-Rican Courses and Personnel (Box 17, Folder 314 - 315)
    - Recommendations (Box 17, Folder 316)
    - Recommendations, Faculty (Box 17, Folder 317)
    - Records (Box 17, Folder 318)
    - Registrar's Office (Box 17, Folder 319 - 320)
    - Registrar's Studies (Box 17, Folder 321)
    - Research (Box 17, Folder 322)
    - Reserve Officers Training Corps (Box 17, Folder 323 - 324)
    - Resident Fellows Requests (Box 17, Folder 325)
    - Residential College System -- Committee to Review (Box 17, Folder 326)
    - Retirement Policy (Box 17, Folder 327)
    - Roper Center (Box 17, Folder 329)
    - Scholars of the House (Box 17, Folder 330 - 331)
    - Science Education, Undergraduate (Box 17, Folder 332)
    - Scientific Magazine, Yale (Box 18, Folder 333 - 334)
    - Secretary's Office (Box 18, Folder 335 - 336)
    - Security (Box 18, Folder 337)
    - Seven Springs (Box 18, Folder 338)
    - Size of Yale College (Box 18, Folder 339 - 340)
    - Slavic (Box 18, Folder 341 - 342)
    - Sophomore Housing (Box 18, Folder 343)
    - Space (Box 18, Folder 344 - 345)
    - Spanish (Box 18, Folder 346 - 348)
    - Special Students (Box 19, Folder 349 - 351)
    - Statistics (Box 19, Folder 352 - 353)
    - Steering Committee (Box 19, Folder 354 - 355)
    - Sterling Scholarships (Box 19, Folder 356)
    - Stiles College, Ezra (Box 19, Folder 357)
    - Student Directory (Box 19, Folder 358)
    - Summer Language Institute (Box 19, Folder 359 - 360)
    - Summer Programs (Box 19, Folder 361 - 362)
    - Summer Programs, Committee on Future (Box 20, Folder 363)
    - Summer Term (Box 20, Folder 364 - 365)
    - Teacher Preparation (Box 20, Folder 366)
    - Teaching Fellows (Box 20, Folder 367 - 368)
    - Teaching and Learning Committee (Box 20, Folder 369 - 372)
    - Telephones (Box 20, Folder 373 - 374)
    - Television (Box 20, Folder 375)
    - Title IX (Box 20, Folder 376 - 377)
    - Transfer Students (Box 21, Folder 378)
    - Treasurer's Office' (Box 21, Folder 380)
    - Tribunal, University-Wide (Box 21, Folder 381 - 382)
    - Truman Scholarship (Box 21, Folder 383)
    - Tutoring (Box 21, Folder 384 - 385)
    - Undergraduate Affairs (Box 21, Folder 386)
    - Undergraduate Organizations (Box 21, Folder 387 - 388)
    - Undergraduate Prizes (Box 21, Folder 389)
    - Undergraduate Regulations (Box 21, Folder 390 - 391)
    - Unification Church (Box 21, Folder 392)
    - University Council (Box 21, Folder 393 - 394)
    - Visiting Committee-Division of Physical Sciences (Box 21, Folder 395)
    - Visitors to Yale (Box 21, Folder 396)
    - WELI (Box 21, Folder 397)
    - Wesleyan-Yale Exchange (Box 21, Folder 398)
    - Whiffenpoofs (Box 21, Folder 399)
    - "Who's Who" Lists (Box 21, Folder 400)
    - Women, Advisory Committee on Education of (Box 21, Folder 401 - 402)
    - Women's Affairs (Box 21, Folder 403 - 404)
    - Women, Brown Coeducation Conference (Box 22, Folder 405)
    - Women's Studies (Box 22, Folder 406 - 407)
    - Woods Hole Oceanographic Institute (Box 22, Folder 408)
    - Writing (Box 22, Folder 409 - 411)
    - Writing Workshop (Box 22, Folder 412)
    - Yacht Club, Yale Faculty (Box 22, Folder 413)
    - Yale-China Association (Box 22, Folder 414 - 415)
    - Yale College, Committees (Box 22, Folder 416)
    - Yale College, Committees -- Special and Standing (Box 22, Folder 417)
    - Yale College Internship Program (Box 22, Folder 418)
    - Yale College Programs of Study (Box 23, Folder 419 - 420)
    - Yale Course of Study Committee (Box 23, Folder 421 - 424)
    - Yale Panoramas (Box 23, Folder 425)
    - Yale Women's Forum (CYC) (Box 23, Folder 426)
  - 1975-1979 -- Restricted Materials
    - Admissions Undergraduate (Box 24, Folder 1)
    - Affirmative Action Approvals (Box 24, Folder 2)
    - Afro-American Cultural Center (Box 24, Folder 3)
    - Applications for Positions (Box 24, Folder 4 - 6)
    - Appointments, Junior (Box 24, Folder 7 - 8)
    - Appointments, Junior and Term (Box 24, Folder 9 - 11)
    - Appointments, Senior Biological Sciences (Box 24, Folder 12 - 13)
    - Appointments, Senior Humanities (Box 25, Folder 14 - 16)
    - Appointments, Senior Physical Sciences (Box 25, Folder 17 - 18)
    - Appointments, Senior Social Sciences (Box 25, Folder 19 - 21)
    - Architecture (Box 25, Folder 22)
    - Art School and Major (Box 25, Folder 23)
    - Band, Yale (Box 25, Folder 24 - 25)
    - Benefits (Box 25, Folder 26)
    - Biology (Box 25, Folder 27)
    - Black Student Alliance at Yale (Box 26, Folder 28)
    - Board of Permanent Officers, Joint (Box 26, Folder 29 - 32)
    - Chemistry (Box 26, Folder 33 - 34)
    - Chicano Students Affair (Box 26, Folder 35)
    - Commencement (Box 26, Folder 36 - 37)
    - Corporation Actions (Box 26, Folder 38)
    - Council of Masters (Box 26, Folder 39 - 41)
    - Deans, Candidates for College (Box 27, Folder 42 - 43)
    - Dean, Applications for Assistant Dean (Box 27, Folder 44)
    - Dean Search (Box 27, Folder 45)
    - Debating (Box 27, Folder 46 - 47)
    - Economics (Box 27, Folder 48)
    - Engineering and Applied Science (Box 27, Folder 49 - 52)
    - Executive Committee, Faculty of Arts and Sciences (Box 28, Folder 53 - 56)
    - Executive Committee Minutes (Box 28, Folder 57 - 58)
    - Executive Committee Yale College (Box 28, Folder 59 - 61)
    - Faculty Fellowships (Box 28, Folder 62)
    - Faculty Meetings (Box 28, Folder 63 - 66)
    - Faculty Meetings (Box 29, Folder 67 - 71)
    - French (Box 29, Folder 72 - 73)
    - Freshman Counselors (Box 29, Folder 74)
    - Garland (Box 29, Folder 75)
    - Geology and Geophysics (Box 29, Folder 76 - 77)
    - German (Box 29, Folder 78 - 79)
    - Grades (Box 29, Folder 82)
    - Grades and Grading (Box 30, Folder 83 - 84)
    - Hatch Prize (Box 30, Folder 88 - 89)
    - History (Box 30, Folder 90 - 91)
    - History of Art (Box 30, Folder 92 - 93)
    - Honorary Degrees (Box 30, Folder 94)
    - Indonesian (Box 30, Folder 95)
    - Institution, Research Office of (Box 30, Folder 96 - 99)
    - Italian (Box 31, Folder 100 - 101)
    - Joint Board Meetings (Box 31, Folder 102)
    - Junior Faculty Fellowships (Box 31, Folder 103)
    - Junior Faculty Fellowships -- Natural Sciences (Box 31, Folder 104 - 106)
    - Junior Faculty Fellowships -- Social Sciences (Box 31, Folder 107 - 110)
    - Leaves of Absence (Box 31, Folder 111)
    - Leaves of Absence Approvals (Box 31, Folder 112)
    - Leaves of Absence Junior Faculty (Box 32, Folder 113 - 114)
    - Leaves of Absence, Request for (Box 32, Folder 115 - 118)
    - Lecturers -- 3/4, 1/2, 1/3 and Part time (Box 32, Folder 119 - 120)
    - Lecturers -- Graduate School (Box 32, Folder 121)
    - Lecturers -- Yale College (Box 32, Folder 122)
    - Letters -- General (Box 32, Folder 123 - 124)
    - Madrical Replacement (Box 32, Folder 125)
    - Managerial and Professional (Box 33, Folder 126)
    - McFarland Case (Box 33, Folder 127)
    - Medical School (Box 33, Folder 128)
    - Molecular Biophysics and Biochemistry (Box 33, Folder 129 - 130)
    - Morse College (Box 33, Folder 135)
    - Morse Fellowships (Box 33, Folder 136 - 138)
    - Morse Fellowships (Box 34, Folder 139 - 140)
    - Music (Box 34, Folder 141 - 142)
    - Near Eastern Languages and Literatures (Box 35, Folder 143 - 144)
    - Nieves-Falcon, Luis (Box 35, Folder 145)
    - Organization and Management, School of (Box 35, Folder 146 - 147)
    - Parent Correspondence (Box 35, Folder 148 - 149)
    - Philosophy (Box 35, Folder 150 - 151)
    - Physics (Box 35, Folder 152 - 153)
    - Political Science (Box 35, Folder 154 - 155)
    - Pre-Medical Advisory Committee (Box 35, Folder 156 - 157)
    - Pre-Registration Orientation Program (Box 35, Folder 158 - 159)
    - Prize Teaching Fellows (Box 35, Folder 160 - 162)
    - Prize Teaching Fellows (Box 36, Folder 163 - 165)
    - Prize Teaching Fellow Responses (Box 36, Folder 166)
    - Prizes, Undergraduate (Box 36, Folder 167)
    - Recommendations (Box 37, Folder 168 - 169)
    - Residential College Seminars (Box 37, Folder 170 - 173)
    - Religious Studies (Box 37, Folder 174)
    - Salaries (Box 37, Folder 175 - 176)
    - Sociology (Box 37, Folder 179 - 180)
    - Strike (Box 38, Folder 181)
    - Student Letters (Box 38, Folder 182 - 183)
    - Student Programs (Box 38, Folder 184 - 185)
    - Summer Letters (Box 38, Folder 186 - 187)
    - Teaching (Box 38, Folder 188 - 189)
    - Teaching in the Residential Colleges (Box 38, Folder 190 - 194)
    - Teaching in the Residential Colleges (Box 39, Folder 195 - 198)
    - Teaching Preparation (Box 40, Folder 199)
    - Theater Studies (Box 40, Folder 200 - 201)
    - Visiting Faculty (Box 40, Folder 202 - 204)
    - Wind, Herbert (Box 40, Folder 205)
    - Women, Search for a Director of the Office on the Education of Women at Yale (Box 40, Folder 206 - 207)
    - Women, Search for a Director of the Office on the Education of Women at Yale (Box 41, Folder 208 - 209)
    - Women's Studies (Box 41, Folder 210 - 211)
    - Yale College, Search for Assistant Associate Dean (Box 41, Folder 212 - 213)
  - Financial Papers, 1973-1979
    - Career Advisory Expenses (Box 42, Folder 1)
    - Casual Payroll (Box 42, Folder 2)
    - Christmas (Box 42, Folder 3)
    - Combined Science (Box 42, Folder 4)
    - Communications (Box 42, Folder 5)
    - Departmental Budgets (Box 42, Folder 6 - 9)
    - DeVane Lectureship (Box 42, Folder 10)
    - Entertainment (Box 42, Folder 11)
    - Executive Assistant (Box 42, Folder 12)
    - Faculty, Yale College (Box 43, Folder 13)
    - Faculty Lists (Box 43, Folder 14)
    - Fair Labor Standard Act Reports (Box 43, Folder 15)
    - Groceries (Box 43, Folder 16)
    - Maintenance Contracts (Box 43, Folder 17)
    - Miscellaneous Purchases (Box 43, Folder 18)
    - Office Furnishings (Box 43, Folder 20)
    - Payroll Distribution Registers (Box 43, Folder 21)
    - Personnel 1973 on (Box 43, Folder 22)
    - Request for Services (Box 43, Folder 23 - 24)
    - Residential College Deans-Budget (Box 43, Folder 25)
    - Stock Requests (Box 43, Folder 26)
    - Summer Orientation Program (Box 43, Folder 27)
    - Summer Term Administration (Box 44, Folder 28)
    - Teaching and Learning (Box 44, Folder 29)
    - Travel (Box 44, Folder 30)
    - Wages and Salary (Box 44, Folder 31)
    - Vacation Schedules (Box 44, Folder 32)
    - Yale College Dean's Office Budget (Box 44, Folder 33)
    - Yale College Dean's Office Staff (Box 44, Folder 34)
- War certificates and pamphlets of the Classes of 1944-1946, 1940-1946; Accession 1986-A-107
  - Lists of war certificates for the classes of 1944, 1945 and 1946 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Pamphlets "Yale Studies for Returning Service Men" and "An Introduction to Yale" (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Snapshot of Yale College Web site, 2010 September; Accession 2012-A-033
  Scope and Contents
  Publications included are Yale College Programs of Study (YCPS), Undergraduate Regulations, Freshman Handbook, Transfer Handbook, the Sophomore Web Site, DUS Handbook, Instructors' Handbook, Residential College Seminar booklet, and Calendar for the Opening Days of College.
  - Snapshot of Yale College Web site, 2010 September; 1838; 8 css, 4 doc, 33 gif, 1599 html, 2 ico, 61 jpg, 2 js, 103 pdf, 19 png, 4 ppt (Box 1)
    Original born digital files, as well as preservation masters, may not be accessed due to their fragility. Researchers must consult use copies, or if none exist request that they be made. Born digital files cannot be accessed remotely. System requirements include a Manuscripts and Archives computer and file viewing software.
- Additional material, 1960-1987; Accession 2016-A-011
  Restricted until January 1, 2022
- Office of Development records, 2009-2012; Accession 2018-A-060
  Restricted until January 1, 2048.
  - Letters from Yale alumni to the Yale College Office of Development in support of naming one of the new residential colleges after Norman Sydney Buck, Master of Branford College (1942-1959)., 2009-2012 (Box 1, Folder 1-3)
- Records of Mary Miller as dean, 1999-2015; Accession 2018-A-062
  The records are restricted until January 1, 2050.
  - Graduate School of Arts and Sciences, 2009-2010 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Yale Institute for Biospheric Studies, 2009 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Interdisciplinary Performance Studies at Yale, 2010 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Intensive Session, Yale National Initiative, 2009 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Light Fellowship, 2010 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Report on Minors Spring 2010-COM (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Directed Studies, 2009-2010 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Masters/ Deans Joint Workshops, 2009 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - National Gallery of Art, 2010 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Mary Miller National Gallery of Art, 2009 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Paul Mellon Centre for Studies in British Art Board of Governors, 2010 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Madame Ninh, Vietnam Visit, 2009 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - DMM- Meetings, 2009 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Greenberg Conference Center Dedication, 2009 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - National University of Singapore, 2010 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - K.Y.Yong, National, 2010 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Opening Days, 2009-2010 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Orientation, 2009 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Freshman Counselor and Peer Liason Reception, 2009 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Freshman Assembly Orientation, 2009 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Freshman Affairs, 2008-2009 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Freshman Address, 2009 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Global Health, 2009-2010 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Orientation, 2009-2010 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Orientation for International Students, 2009-2010 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Panel Discussion for Parents and Families, 2010 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Peer Liason Program, 2009-2010 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - LGBTQ, 2009-2010 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Pre Registration Meeting Agenda, 2009-2010 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Mellon Foundation Proposal, 2010 Spring (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Mellon Lectures, 2010 Spring (Box 1, Folder 36-37)
  - Mellon Foundation, 2009 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Mixed Gender Housing, 2009-2010 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Mary Miller- Peabody Essex Museum, 2009-2010 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - NEASC, 2010 (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - NEASC Reaccreditation Visit, 2009 (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - PKU, 2009-2010 (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - Prize Teaching Fellowship, 2009-2010 (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - Sheffield Society Houze Prize, 2009-2010 (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - Poorvu, Greer Prizes, 2009-2010 (Box 1, Folder 50-51)
  - Heyman Prizes, 2009-2010 (Box 1, Folder 52-53)
  - Residential Colleges, 2009 (Box 1, Folder 54)
  - New Residential Colleges Steering Committee, 2009-2010 (Box 1, Folder 55)
  - Executive Residential College Meetings, 2009-2010 (Box 1, Folder 56)
  - Assistant Provost Search, 2009 (Box 1, Folder 57)
  - Web director, 2009 (Box 1, Folder 58)
  - Director, Office of Faculty Affairs, 2009 (Box 1, Folder 59)
  - Assistant Provost Search, Di Bonaventura Allegra, 2009 (Box 1, Folder 60)
  - Associate Dean for International Affairs, 2006 (Box 1, Folder 61)
  - Director of Web Strategy, 2009 (Box 1, Folder 62)
  - Afro-American Cultural Center Dean Search, 2010 Spring (Box 1, Folder 63)
  - Recording Secretary, Office of, 2010 (Box 1, Folder 64)
  - Secretary's- Yale University, 2007 (Box 1, Folder 65)
  - Security, 2007-2008 (Box 1, Folder 66)
  - Security, 2009-2010 (Box 1, Folder 67)
  - History of Sexualities, 2009 (Box 1, Folder 68)
  - Yale Anniversaries Conference WGSS & LGBTS, 2010 (Box 1, Folder 69)
  - Shape Report, 2009-2010 (Box 1, Folder 71)
  - Rape and Sexual Violence Prevention, 2009-2010 (Box 1, Folder 72)
  - STARS, 2009-2010 (Box 1, Folder 73)
  - Stationery, Mary Miller, Undated (Box 1, Folder 74)
  - Letters of Recommendation (Miller), 2010-2011 (Box 1, Folder 75)
  - United Arab Emirates Drs. Courtney Stryker and Nancy Dye, 2009-2010 (Box 1, Folder 76)
  - Sterling Fellows, Undated (Box 1, Folder 77)
  - Summer Plans, 2009 (Box 1, Folder 78)
  - Swine Flu, 2009 (Box 1, Folder 79)
  - Teaching Fellows, 2010 (Box 1, Folder 80)
  - Tobacco Free Yale workgroup, 2010 (Box 1, Folder 81)
  - Travel, Mary Miller, Undated (Box 1, Folder 82)
  - University Budget, 2009-2010 (Box 1, Folder 83)
  - Yale Women's Conference, 2010 (Box 1, Folder 84)
  - Website Design, Undated (Box 1, Folder 85)
  - Yale CollegeWeb Site Planning, 2009-2010 (Box 1, Folder 86)
  - World Fellows, 2009-2010 (Box 1, Folder 87)
  - Writing Center, 2009-2010 (Box 1, Folder 88)
  - Yale Shuttle, 2009-2010 (Box 1, Folder 89)
  - Yale Symphony, 2009-2010 (Box 1, Folder 90)
  - Yale Club, Undated (Box 1, Folder 91)
  - Yale College Council, Undated (Box 1, Folder 92)
  - Yale University Art Gallery, Undated (Box 1, Folder 93)
  - Mellon Mays Undergrad. Fellowship Program, Annual Program Report, 2009-2010 (Box 1, Folder 94)
  - The Napier Initiative, Undated (Box 1, Folder 95)
  - NUS, 2010-2011 (Box 1, Folder 96)
  - OIR, 2009-2011 (Box 1, Folder 97-98)
  - Miller, Mary OIS Orientation, 2010-2011 (Box 1, Folder 99)
  - Resdential Colleges, 2010-2011 (Box 1, Folder 100)
  - Student Affairs Fellows Search, Spring 2010 (Box 1, Folder 101)
  - Student Affairs Fellow Candidate Aisha Coradin, Undated (Box 1, Folder 102)
  - Alcohol Policy, 2010-2011 (Box 1, Folder 103)
  - Bulldog Days, 2010 (Box 1, Folder 104)
  - Freshman Asembly, 2010-2011 (Box 1, Folder 105)
  - Fershman Handbook, 2010-2011 (Box 1, Folder 106)
  - Froco/ Peer Liaisons Reception, 2010-2011 (Box 1, Folder 107)
  - Reminder Notes for 2010-2011 (Box 1, Folder 108)
  - Scripts, 2010-2011 (Box 1, Folder 109)
  - Sex@Yale Initiative, Undated (Box 1, Folder 110)
  - Sustainability, 2010, Undated (Box 1, Folder 111-112)
  - Teacher's Institute-Josiah Brown, Undated (Box 1, Folder 113)
  - Teaching, Undated (Box 1, Folder 114)
  - Undergraduate Regulations, 2010-2011 (Box 1, Folder 115)
  - Yale Club, Undated (Box 1, Folder 116)
  - Academic Affairs-Correspondence, Undated (Box 1, Folder 117)
  - Bouchet Undergraduate Residential Fellowship, 2009-2010 (Box 1, Folder 118)
  - Academic Calendars, 2009-2010 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - ACE Fellows, 2009-2010 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Renee Barnett Terry, Ph.D, American Council on Education (ACE) Fellow, 2009-2010 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Advising Ressources in Yale College, 2010 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Arts, 0 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Animal Behavior (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Arts at Yale, 2010 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Arts and Architecture, 2009 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Ad hoc Committee on Mayor's report, 1999-2000 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Athletics, 2009-2010 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Bladder Ball, 2009-2010 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Class of 2013, 2009 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Committee Confidentiality Statements, 2010 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Fellowship Committees, 2009-2010 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Fellowships Dinner, Spring 2010 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Committee on Majors, 2010 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Committees, Office of the Provost, 2009 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Committee on Yale's Role in Helping Students Reason through their Occupational Decisions, 2008-2009 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Consortium for Language, Teaching and Learning, 2009-2010 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Correspondence, 2009-2010 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Community Based Learning, 2009 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Council of Masters, 2009-2011 (Box 2, Folder 22-24)
  - Council of Masters Chair, 2009 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Implementing Committee on Yale College Education Recommendations, 2009 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Corporation, 2009-2010 (Box 2, Folder 28-30)
  - Cultural centers, 2009-2010 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - CYCE, 2009 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - NYC Development Trip- Development, 2010 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Development Campaign Report, 2010 (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - NYC Development Trip, 2010 (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - MM-CA DEV, TRIP, 2010 (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - Yale Legacy Partners, 2010 (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - Development Correspondence, 2009-2010 (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - Directed Independent Language Study, 2008-2009 (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - Classroom Interruptions-MM e-mail Responses, 2010 (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - Dwight Hall at Yale- Center for Public Service and Social Justice, Undated (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - Eli Whitney Program, Undated (Box 2, Folder 46)
  - Events Attended- Dean Mary Miller, 2009-2010 (Box 2, Folder 47)
  - 40th Anniversay of Co-education, 2009 (Box 2, Folder 48)
  - Installation Design and the Silenced Art Object- Art of the Ancient Americas at LACMA, 2009 (Box 2, Folder 49)
  - Ivy China Summit, 2009 (Box 2, Folder 50)
  - Post Baccalaureate Reception, 2009 (Box 2, Folder 51)
  - The Saybrook Portrait or Mary Miller, Edwards Kamens, and their cat, Rainbow, 2009 (Box 2, Folder 52)
  - Women's Faculty Forum Working Group on Sexual Misconduct and Misogyny, 2009 (Box 2, Folder 53)
  - Women Faculty Forum, 2009 (Box 2, Folder 54)
  - Women Leadership Initiative, 2009-2010 (Box 2, Folder 55)
  - Mary Miller-Forms, 2009-2010 (Box 2, Folder 56)
  - Family Weekend, 2009 (Box 2, Folder 57)
  - Yale Global Health Initiative, 2009 (Box 2, Folder 59)
  - All staff Meetings, Yale College, 2009-2010 (Box 2, Folder 60)
  - All staff metting, 2008-2009 (Box 2, Folder 61)
  - Associate Dean's meetings, 2010-2011 (Box 2, Folder 62)
  - Associate Dean's meetings, 2011-2012 (Box 2, Folder 63)
  - Associate Dean's meetings, 2012-2013 (Box 2, Folder 64)
  - Announcements, 2008-2009 (Box 2, Folder 65)
  - AED-SSS, 2015 (Box 2, Folder 66)
  - Associate Dean's meetings, 2010 (Box 2, Folder 67)
  - Associate Dean's meetings, 2007-2008 (Box 2, Folder 68)
  - Associate Dean's meetings, 2009-2010 (Box 2, Folder 69)
  - YC Associate Deans meeting, 2010-2011 (Box 2, Folder 70)
  - Associate Dean's meetings, 2007-2008 (Box 2, Folder 71)
  - Associate Dean's meetings, 2008-2009 (Box 2, Folder 72)
  - Associate Dean's meetings, 2009-2010 (Box 2, Folder 73)
  - Yale club scholarships-northup (deceased), Undated (Box 2, Folder 74)
  - Dean of Student Affairs Search, 2015 (Box 2, Folder 75)
  - Yale College Development, 2011-2012 (Box 2, Folder 76)
  - DUS lists, 2004-2005 (Box 2, Folder 77)
  - Environmental Studies, Undated (Box 2, Folder 78)
  - Ivy plus Deans, 2009 (Box 2, Folder 79)
  - Mellon Foundation, 2013 (Box 2, Folder 83)
  - Mellon workshops, 2013 (Box 2, Folder 84)